HAYTHAM KHAMAISI

Email: haythamkhmaisi@gmail.com Phone: 0522977818



OBJECTIVE

A 2nd year Information Systems Management student with a solid academic background and a comprehensive skill set, and highly capable of attention to details. Underpinned by experience in pressurized situations necessitating self-motivation and positive response to pressure. Committed team player with leadership ability, fast learner, with high standards of communication to establish positive interpersonal relationships; quick and willing to assimilate and apply new work procedures.



EDUCATION

2019 – 2021 | B.A. in Information Systems Management | Ben Gurion University

Ability to time management, work in a team environment with professional integrity and demonstrated leadership, management orientation, learn and solve problems, and able to manage work in high pressure conditions

Relevant Course:

- Fundamentals of Accounting (83)
- Computer Programming in Java (82)
- Introduction to Marketing (85)
- Introduction to Operations Research (90)
- Data Bases (82)
- Information Systems Analysis and Design(87)
- Foundations of Algorithms and Complexity(85)
- Digital Systems for Electrical and Computer Engineering (79)
- Introduction to Statistics for Management (89)
- Introduction to Economics for Management (85)
- Object Oriented Software Development (87)
- IT Infrastructure (85)
- Information Systems Strategy and Management(83)



EXPERIENCE

2018 - NOW | Academic Tutor

Academic tutor for JAVA, Mathematical Courses and Object-Oriented Software Development at Ben-Gurion University.

2018 - NOW | "Perah" Tutor

Tutoring high school students (mathematics and physics)

2016 – 2017 | "Begrot" (Matriculation exam) tutor

Matriculation exam's courses tutoring for high school students in mathematical calculation.



PROJECTS

- Preliminary analysis of the entity-relationships model, conversion to a tabular model, establishment of a database, queries and applications.
- Designing a new system, this step includes building a database and using UML charts and also developing a prototype of the system using C # software and a database.



SKILLS

HTML

- JAVA
- Python
- Database Management (SQL)
- EXCEL

MY-SOL

- Statistics
- Windows/Linux Environment
 - Object-Oriented Programming
- Measurement Evaluation
- Management Information Systems

...

LANGUAGE

English: Professional | Hebrew: expert | Arabic- Mother Tongue.